Guide to the New Dimensions Media records M1577
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Accession 2008-144
  - Sub-Series 6: Newsletters, Program Guides and information about New Dimensions as an organization, 6
    - New Dimensions Radio Newsletter, 2003 (Half-box 154, Folder 3)
    - New Dimensions Radio Newsletter, 2004 (Half-box 154, Folder 4)
    - New Dimensions Radio Newsletter, 2005 (Half-box 154, Folder 5)
    - New Dimensions Radio Newsletter, 2006 (Half-box 154, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 7: Photographs, 7
    Many photos include Michael Tom and/or Justine Tom with the guest but theToms names are not listed.
    Photographs of guests who appeared on New Dimensions.
    - Abbey, Edward (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Abrams, Jeremiah (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Aburdene, Patricia (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Abukhalil, Asad (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Achterberg, Jeanne (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Adair, Margot (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Adrienne, Carol (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Alexander, Shoshana (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Allegretti, Jan (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Allen, Marc (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Allende, Isabel (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Allen, Paula Gunn (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Alt, Jeff (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Altemus, Barbara (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Alter, Joel and Cheri Quincy (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Anderson, Sherry and Paul Rey, Patricia Hopkins (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Anderson, Nancy (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Anderson, William (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Anreas, Connirare (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Andrews, Lynn (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Angelou, Maya (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Ansary, Tamin (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Apollon, Susan (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - Ardagh, Arjuna (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Arguelles, Jose and Lloydine Arguelles (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - Arkin, Alan (Box 155, Folder 24)
    - Angeles, Arrien (Box 155, Folder 25)
    - Armstrong, David and Elizabeth Armstrong (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - Armstrong, Karen (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - Armstrong, Ann and Jim Armstrong (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - Artress, Lauren (Box 155, Folder 27)
    - Arvigo, Rosita (Box 155, Folder 28)
    - Atlee, Tom and Jay Early (Box 155, Folder 29)
    - Austen, James (Box 155, Folder 30)
    - Ausubel, Kenny and Nina Simons (Box 155, Folder 31)
    - Autry, James (Box 155, Folder 32)
    - "A" letter guests: Robert Allen, Tsuitrim Allione, John and Kris Amodeo, John Avedon, Antero Alli, W. Agor, Carl Anthony with Chellis Glendinning, Carol Augustus, Theresa Sheppard Alexander, The Atomic Comics (Box 155, Folder 33)
    - Bache, Chris and Winston Franklin (Box 155, Folder 34)
    - Bagby, Rachel (Box 155, Folder 34)
    - Barasch, Mark (Box 155, Folder 35)
    - Barks, Coleman (Box 155, Folder 36)
    - Barlow, Connie and Michael Dowd (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Barrantes, Willie (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Barzakov, Ivan (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Batchelor, Stephen (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Beak, Sera (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Beattie, Melody (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Bedford, Jane (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Beinfield, Harriet and Efrem Korngold (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Bennett, Hal (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Berg, Peter (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Bernie, Barbara (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Berry, Wendell and Thomas Berry (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Donovan, Bess (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Beyondananda, Swami (Steve Bhaerman) (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Birnbaum, Ed (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Bloom, Charley and Linda Bloom (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Bloomfield, John and Harold Bloomfield, Sirah Bloomfield, Robert Cooper (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Blum, Ralph (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Bly, Robert (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Bohm, David; Mrs. Bohm and Michael Toms and Justine Toms at Ojai (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Bolen, Jean Shinoda (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Boorstein, Sylvia (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Bosnak, Robert (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Bowles, Beatrice (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Boyd, Andrew (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Boyd, Doug (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Bradshaw, John (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Brady, Leah and Lee Brady, Diana James (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Brand, Stewart (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Branden, Nathaniel (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Barungart, Michael and William McDonough (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Breema and Denise Berezonsky, Jon Schreiber, Angela Porter (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Brener, Anne (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Brennan, Barbara (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Brezsny, Rob (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Briskin, Alan (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Broomfield, John (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Brower, David (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Brown, Fred (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Brown, Jerry (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Brown, David Isaacs and Juanita Brown (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Borysenko, Joan (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Brussat, Mary Ann and Fredric Brussat (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Bruyere, Rosalyn (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Budapest, Zsuzsanna (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Burnum, Burnum (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Byron, Katie (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - "B" letter guests: Barbara Brennan, Peter Berg, Spencer Brewer, Tony Buzan, John Bradshaw, Thomas Banyaca, Michael Brown, Richard, Bach, Bud Berglund, Lonnie Barbuch, Jalaja Bonheim, Steve Bhaerman, Coleman Barks, Allan Hunt Badiner, Jeannine Parvati Baker; photos in Bali; one unidentified 8x10 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Cahill, Sedonia (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Caldicott, Helen (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Cameron, Julia and Tim Wheater (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Campbell, Bebe Moore (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Campbell, Don (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Campbell, Joseph (Box 157, Folder 6)
      Two negative strips and contact sheets; one negative of Campbell with Michael Toms
    - Capacchione, Lucia (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Capra, Fritjof (Box 157, Folder 7)
      One slide
    - Carey, Ken (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Carney, Teddy and Otis Carney (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Carison, Don and Craig Comstock (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Carse, James (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Catalfo, Phil (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Chakravarti, Sree (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Chang, Iris (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Chidananda, Brother (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Chupich, Erika and Margaret Paul (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Chopra, Deepak (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Christ, Carol (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Christian, Diana (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Clements, Alan (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Cleveland, Harlan (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Cochran, Tracy (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Cody, Anna (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Cole-Whittaker, Terry (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Combs, Deidre (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Cooper, Jay (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Cooper, Rabbi David (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Cousens, Gabril (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Cousineau, Phil (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Craighead, Meinrad (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Croswell, Ken (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Crow, Thomas (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Crum, Tom (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Cummings, Mark and Jasmuheen Cummings (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Cusumano, Joseph (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Csikszentmihalyi, Mihaly (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - "C" letter guests: Cherie Carter-Scott, Allan Cox, Arthur Cox, Robert Cromey, David Carson, Bruce Cockburn, Paula Carroll, Peter Carroll, Rodrigo Carazo, Sylvie Crockett, Paul Crockett, Susan Campbell, Tom Cooper; photocopy of Alex Counts (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - D'Amore, Louis and Pat Lawrence (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Dahl, Lynda (Box 158, Folder 3)
      Negative strip
    - Dalai Lama on Mt. Tamalpais, black and white (Box 157, Folder 4)
      Negative strips
    - Danaher, Kevin and Medea Benjamin (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Dantes, Ligia (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Darling, Davia and Diana Darling (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Davies, Paul (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Elizabeth (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - Daas, Ram (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Day, Laura (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Debold, Elizabeth (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Delaney, Gail (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - della Madre, Leslene and Jerrygrace Lyons (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - de Quincey, Christian (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Devadeson, Tania (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Diaz, Adriana (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Disharoon, Mary (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Dizerega, Gus (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Dominguez, Joe and Robin Dominguez, Vicki Dominguez (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Dossey, Larry and Marilyn Schlitz (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Dreamer, Orlah Mountain (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Duff, Kat (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Dyer, Wayne (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - "D" letter guests: Davis, Bruce, Genny Davis, Arthur Deikman, Peter Dawkins, Ken, Dychtwald, Judith Dubin, Jesse Darrell, Mitani D'Antien, Murshida Ivey Duce, Jim Dodge, and Deep Ecology for the 21st Century (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Erhard, Werner (Box 158, Folder 13)
      10 color slides
    - Eisen, Saul (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Eisler, Riane and David Loye (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Ekins, Paul (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Elgin, Duane (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Ellis, Dave (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Elmer, Lon (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Emery, Stewart (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Emoto, Dr. (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Ensler, Eve (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Epstein, Mark (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Estes, Clarissa Pinkola (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - "E" letter guests: Easwaran Eknath, Stewart Emery, David Easton (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Fadiman, Jim and Dorothy Fadiman (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - Feinstein, David and Peg Mayo (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Ferguson, Tom and Marilyn Ferguson (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Fields, Rick (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Finley, Guy (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Findeisen, Barbara and Bruce Lipton, Margo Heiniger-White (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - F.I.R.E.: Katerina Anfossi, Geneviev VAughan, Maria Suarez (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Fix, Ray (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Flatischer, Reinhard and Cornelia Reinhard, Heidrun Hoffman (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Fleming, Peggy (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Fletcher, Colin (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Flinders, Carol Lee (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Ford, Clyde (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Ford, Debbie (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Foreman, Dave (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Forsee, David (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Fox, Matthew (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Frager, Robert (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Franick, Frederick and Claske Franick (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Franklin, Winston and Chris Bache (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Frantzis, Bruce Kumar (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Friend, Gil (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Fritz, Robert (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Frock, Linda (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Frock, Roger (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Fuller, Millard (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Fuller, Robert and Alia Johnson, Robert Cabot, Bec (?) (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Fuigham, Robert (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - "F" letter guests: Sharon Franquemont, Steve Fotter, Timothy Ferris, Meredith and Steven Little-Foster, Lilias Folan (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Galland, China (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Gangaji (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Gardner, Barbara (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Garfield, Charles and Sedonia Cahill (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Gaskin, Stephen (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Gass, Robert (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Gates, Jeff (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - Gawain, Shakti and Adelide Bry (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - Gelb, Michael (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - Gendler, Ruth (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - George, Demetra (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - George, Jay and Julia Globus-Sabori (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Gebner, George (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Gerzon, Mark (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Gignoux, Jane (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Gilman, Robert (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - Gimbutas, Marija and Joan Marler (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - Ginsberg, Allen (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Giovanni, Nikki (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Glasser, Harold (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Glendinning, Chellis (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Glickstein, Lee (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Goldberg, Burton (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Goldberg, Natalie (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Goldman, Andi and Jonathan Goldman (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Goleman, Daniel and Tara Bennet Goleman (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Goodall, Jane (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Goswami, Amit (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Gottlieb, Freema (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Grabowsky, Mary Ford (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Grandin, Temple (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Gray, Leslie (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Greider, William (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Griffin, Susan (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Griffiths, Fr. Bede (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Grof, Stanislav and Willis Harman (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Gumbleton, Bishop Thomas (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Gurian, Michael (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - "G" letter guests: Patricia Garfield, His Holiness Gyalwa Karmapa, Jhn Gray, Michael Grosso, Rosemary Gladstar, Uri Geller, Laeh Maggie Garfield, Mark Goldes, Sim Van der Ryn, Gyuto Monks (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Haas, Elson (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Halifax, Joan (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Halpern, Steven (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Halprin, Sara (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Hamburg, Dan (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Hamilton, Craig (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Hamilton, Vijali (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Hammer, Grace Yellow (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Vazquez, Debora and Francisco Vasquez (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Hannaford, Carla (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Harak, Father G. Simon, S.J. (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Harvey, Andrew and Lela Landman, Jane Heaven (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Harding, Douglas (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Harman, Willis and Rachel Remen, Juanita Brown (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Harner, Michael (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Hart, Mickey (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Hatman, Thom (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Harney, Corbin (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Harris, Kirby and Mrs. Harris (?) (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Harris, Sam (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Hastings, Anne Stirling (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Hawken, Paul and James Ogilvy (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Hay, Louise (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Healing Heart of Diversity: Pat Harbour, Shirley Strong, Amshatar Monroe, Martina Whelshula, Lous Ervin, Paul Schultz, Sally Huang-Nissen, Thomas Roosevelt (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - Heerman, Barry (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Heinberg, Richard (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Hienze, Ruth-Inge (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Henderson, Hazel (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Hendricks, Gay and Kathlyn Henricks (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Hermach, Tim and Ted Peters (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Hertsgaard, Mark (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - High Bear, Martin and Woableza, Rose Dreyer (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Hightower, Jim (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Highwater, Jamake (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Geoffrey, Hill (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Hil, Julia Butterfly (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Hirshfield, Jane (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Hirschmann, Jane and Carol Munter (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Hixon, Lex (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Hock, Dee (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Hoffman, David (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Horn, Frances (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Hourigan, James (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Houston, Jean (Box 161, Folder 6)
      Two slides
    - Hubbard, Barbara Mark (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Hubbard, Earl (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Huerta, Dolores (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Huffines, La Una (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - "H" letter guests: Thich Nhat Hanh, Paul Hwochinsky, Beth Hedva, Gail Holland, Basil Hiley, Albert Hogman, Helena Norberg-Hodge, Peggy Huddlesto, Mickey Hart and Zakir Hussain, Paul Horn, Laura Archera Huxley, Andrew Harvey, Richard Strozzi Heckler (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - "H" letter guests: Chungliang Al Huang with Jerry Lynch (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Healing Journey Cancer Conference, Monterey, CA, April 2-3, 1994 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Ingram Catherine (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Inglehart, Hallie Austin and Karen Vogel (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Ingerman, Sandra (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Iyengar, B.K.S. (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - ITA conference, Ireland, 1994, including Norrin Ni Riain and Raam Daas (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Wes (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Jampolsy, Gerald and Diane Cirincione (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Janiger, Oscar (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Jarman, Beth and George Land (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Jarrett, Keith (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Jasmuheen and Mark Cummings (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Jayanti, Sr. (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Jayapal, Premila (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Eli, Jaxon-Bear (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Jeffers, Susan (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Jensen, Robert (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Johnson, John (Box 161, Folder 16)
      - Johnston, Charles (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Bill T. (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Jones, David (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Mary and Pam Colorado, Edme Landeo (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Jones, Michael (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Jones, Ron (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Joy, Brugh (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Judith, Anodea (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Justice on Wheels (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - "J" letter guests: Suki Jay Rappaport, Mark Juergensmeyer, Diana James (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Kabat-Zinn, Jon (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Kalchuri, Bhau and Marilyn McGivney (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Kalu Rinpoche and Lama Lodro (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Karpinski, Gloria (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Karunamayi (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Kasl, Charlotte and Lea Arellano (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Kaye, Les (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Keen, Sam (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Keischnick, Michael (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Kennedy, Alexandra (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Kenley, Joan (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Kessler, Shelley and Rachel Kessler (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Kesten, Deborah (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Kevelis, Melanie (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Kim, Tae Yun (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - King, Marilyn (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Kircher, Pamela (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Klein, Allen (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Kobaly, Robin and Doug Tompkins (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Kornfield, Jack (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Korten, David (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Kramer, Joel and Diana Alstad (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Krishnamurti, J. (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Krohnen, Michael (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Kudler, David (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Kumar, Satish (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Kunsang, Erik Pema (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Swami Kriananda (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - "K" letter guests: Lama Khenpo Konchog Gyaltsen, Myron Kellner-Rogers, Barry Neil Kaufman, Joe Kogel, Jean Klein (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - "K" letter guests: Jon Klimo, John Kimmey, Ken Keyes, Stanley Keleman, Kanya Kekumbha, Marilyn and Robert Kriegel, Donald Keyes, Paul Kivel, Jerry Klein, Pir Vilayat Khan, Hans Kung, Stanley Krippner, Ken Kesey, U. G. Krishnamurti (Box 162, Folder 14)
      Slide of Stanley Krippner
    - LaChappelle, David (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - LaDuke, Betty (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - LaDuke, Winona (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Lama Lodo (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Lancaster, Brad (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Lanmen, Cecilia (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Lapid-Bagda, Ginger (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Lappe, Frances Moore and Anna Lappe (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Larsen, Stephen and Robin Larsen (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Leary, Timothy (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Legendre, Bokara (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Leider, Richard and Mrs. Leider (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Leonard, George (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Leonard, Linda (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Lerner, MIchael Rabbi (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Lesser, Elizabeth (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Levasseur, Conrad (Box 163, Folder 3)
      One disc with journal images
    - Levenson, Robert (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Levine, Stephen and Ondrea Levine (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Levy, Steven (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Liberman, Jacob (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Lietaer, Bernard (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Lippi, Toinette (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Lipton, Bruce (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Lithman, Alan (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Loeb, Paul (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Longaker, Christine (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Lookinghorse, Arvol and Carole Ann Heart (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Loye, David (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Lozoff, Bo (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Luhrs, Janet (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Lyons, Jerrygrace (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - "L" letter guests: Lama Lodru, Michael Lerner, Jan LIttle, James Lovelock, J and S Lanier, George Leonard, Jerry Lynch, Sara Lawrence-Lightfoot, Frederick Leboyer, Gay Luce, Gregg Levoy, Cominique Lapierre, Larkin, Maggie Lettvin, Mike Luedde (Box 163, Folder 9-10)
    - Ma, Chalambla (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Macy, Joanna (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Mackey, Mary (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Ryan-Madson, Patricia (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Maitland, Armaud (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Malkin, Gary and Michael Stillwater (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Mander, Jerry (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Mansfield, Victor (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Marshak, David and Joan Jaeckel (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Mariposa Monarcha (Box 163, Folder 14)
      One strip of negative
    - Markova, Dawna (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Marks, Linda (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Marler, Joan (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Marlin, Alice Tepper (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Marrin, West (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Mason, Marilyn and Rob Pasich (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Masters, Robert (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Mathieu, Allaudin (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Matthiessen, Peter and Roshi Bernard Tetsugan Glassman (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - Mitchell, May (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - McClure, Michael (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - McCoy, Harold (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - McDougall, John (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - McGaa-Eagleman, Ed (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - McKenna, Terence (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - McKeown, Ciarran (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - McLaughlin, Corinne and Gordon Davidson (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - McNiff, Shaun (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Meade, Michael (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Means, Russell (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Medhi, Sharon (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Medicine-Eagle, Brooke (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Meeker, Joe (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Metcalf, Barbara (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Metz, Katherine (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Metger, Deena (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Metzner, Ralph (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Meyers, Kay (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Meyers, Robin (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Emmett and Martin Rossman (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Stuart (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Sukie (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Miller, William (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Millman, Dan (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Mills, Stephanie (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Mindell, Arny and Amy Mnidell (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Mipham, Sakyong (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Mishlove, Jeffrey (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Mitchell, Edgar (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Mitchell, Stephen and James Autry (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Montag, Susan (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Montaldo, Jonathan (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery, Sy (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Moody, Bruce (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Moody, Raymond Jr. (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Moore, Robert (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Moore, Thomas (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Morgan, Marlo (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Morrissey, Mary Manin (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Moss, Richard and Patricia Sun (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Mota, Carlos (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Oriah Mountain Dreamer (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Mountain, Tony (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Mousalam, Barbara (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Moyers, Bill (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Muller, Robert (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Murphy, Michael (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Murphy, Millard (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Myss, Caroline (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Merton Trip, December 1993 (also see Ron Seitz) (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Mindwalk (Box 164, Folder 18)
      Black and white negative of Sam Waterson, John Heard and Liv Ullmann.